{
  "data": [
        {
            "question": "Everyone who works in this department uses ___ computer.",
            "a": "a",
            "b": "an",
            "c": "the",
            "d": "-",
            "answer": "1",
            "explain": "- a (n) + countable nouns\n- we use \"a\" before words that begin with consonants",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "1",
            "subcategorylv2": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "Can you repair _____ computer in Liam's office? It's not working.",
            "a": "a",
            "b": "an",
            "c": "the",
            "d": "-",
            "answer": "3",
            "explain": "- the computer in Liam's office (It is clear in the situation)",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "1",
            "subcategorylv2": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "Excuse me. Is there _____ bank near here?",
            "a": "a",
            "b": "an",
            "c": "the",
            "d": "-",
            "answer": "1",
            "explain": "- a (n) + countable nouns\n- we use \"a\" before words that begin with consonants",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "1",
            "subcategorylv2": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "Please don't stand in front of me. I can't see _____ television.",
            "a": "a",
            "b": "an",
            "c": "the",
            "d": "-",
            "answer": "3",
            "explain": "- the television (it is clear in the situation)",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "1",
            "subcategorylv2": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "Helen had eggs and bacon for _____ breakfast so she wasn't very hungry at lunchtime.",
            "a": "a",
            "b": "an",
            "c": "the",
            "d": "-",
            "answer": "4",
            "explain": "- We use: have something for breakfast",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "1",
            "subcategorylv2": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "When Nigel was promoted at work he moved to a bigger office at _____ end of the corridor.",
            "a": "a",
            "b": "an",
            "c": "the",
            "d": "-",
            "answer": "3",
            "explain": "- We use: at the end of",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "1",
            "subcategorylv2": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "The train to Liverpool will depart from _____ platform 7 in ten minutes. Will passengers please board the train now.",
            "a": "a",
            "b": "an",
            "c": "the",
            "d": "-",
            "answer": "4",
            "explain": "- We use: depart from platform 1, 2, 3, ect ...",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "1",
            "subcategorylv2": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "Sarah went to _____ theatre with some friends to see Shakespeare's 'Hamlet'.",
            "a": "a",
            "b": "an",
            "c": "the",
            "d": "-",
            "answer": "3",
            "explain": "- We use: go to the theatre",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "1",
            "subcategorylv2": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "Neil likes to listen to _____ radio while he is getting dressed.",
            "a": "a",
            "b": "an",
            "c": "the",
            "d": "-",
            "answer": "3",
            "explain": "- We use: listen to the radio but watch TV",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "1",
            "subcategorylv2": "2"
        },
        {
            "question": "Be careful. Radiation from _____ sun can cause skin cancer.",
            "a": "a",
            "b": "an",
            "c": "the",
            "d": "-",
            "answer": "3",
            "explain": "- We use: the sun (only one sun)",
            "category": "1",
            "subcategorylv1": "1",
            "subcategorylv2": "2"
        }
    ]
}